All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, set sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I will be the king of the pirates!
Two years have passed since the war in Marineford.
Each of the Straw Hat Pirates underwent individual training and reunited at the Sabaody Archipelago,
ready to take the next step into the New World.
We're off to Fishman Island!
Wait a sec. What is that thing? A fish? No.
Are you ready? We only get one shot at this!
Ready, brother!
Ready, Captain!
Before you say anything, I know what you're thinking.
Hey, you guys! There's a ship-looking thing coming our way!
Charge!
It's a pirate ship!
Deadly combat under the sea! The demon of the ocean strikes!
Run!
Hard support, now!
Attack them, sea cow!
They're tenacious, aren't they?
That sound!
They don't know when to quit!
Who are these guys after?
The bubble's about to pop!
Keep it up, sea cow!
Yeah!
You think they want to board the ship?
Sea cow?
I know that noise from somewhere!
The two bubbles are touching!
This is a big moment, brother!
Good!
Is everybody ready?
Yeah!
Mumu, it's me!
We've met before!
You're from the Arlong Pirates, right?
Do you remember me?
Nami!
I was at Arlong Park!
Hey, Luffy, doesn't that thing look kind of familiar?
I don't know.
No!
Gum gum pistol!
Let's pay our new friends a visit, shall we?
Yeah!
Hey, that guy's up to something!
Stay out of it!
Guess he's looking for a fight, then!
There's no time to waste!
Follow my lead!
No!
Fools!
They're completely dumbfounded!
If they're gonna sit there catching flies, then we'll strike while the iron is hot!
We'll smite this entire crew!
Right now!
For glory!
Yeah!
Come along, men!
We'll make the beggars for mercy!
What's wrong, Seacal?
Don't panic!
That's not good!
We left Captain Terrible on the ship back there!
Never!
Now, it's time for a little greeting!
Fire the Gatling gun, men!
Shower them in bullets!
I want every last one of them dead!
Send these straw hats to hell!
Huh?
What?!
I don't know!
It's time for a little greeting!
Fire the Gatling gun, men!
Shower them in bullets!
I want every last one of them dead!
Send these straw hats to hell!
Huh?
No! Wait! You're not going to throw me into the water, are you?
Please don't do that to me, my friend! I'm begging you!
Come on! You're a reasonable fellow, are you not?
By the way, you're very good-looking!
I'm sure someone like you understands the value of human life, right?
And besides, the gods are watching! You'll be judged for this!
Oh, make up your freaking mind already!
Weren't you just about to fire your Gatling gun and blast us all to kingdom come?
Me? No! I was just, uh, I was just joking around!
I ain't laughing.
Anyway, tell me. I know you're the captain of that ship, but what's your name?
That's Roro no Zoro!
Don't be ridiculous! What in the world makes you think I would be the captain?
I'm, uh, oh! Those ruffians were keeping me as a, a slave! That's it!
Boy! Ooh! Glad that's over!
You know we're not buying this, right?
Say, how's this? Do you think I could stay on this nice ship with you all for a little while?
Huh? Please?
Wow. I feel kind of sorry for this poor loser.
He's obviously lying! Are you crazy?
What? Seriously?
Hey, I have a question. Where'd that giant sea cow pulling your ship come from?
Hello?
Oh my.
Who's this vixen?
I take it you're the famous cat burglar?
Watch it, pal! Nobody's allowed to drool over our beautiful navigator except for me!
Hey, don't worry. You're perfectly se...
Oh!
Hey, that's getting really old! Cut it out!
The sea cow? Who knows? I just happened to catch it out in the ocean somewhere!
When you're underwater, having a sea monster pull your ship is the mark of an experienced captain!
Huh?
Awesome!
Stop it, sea cow! What's the problem?
Brother! We're on our way to rescue you!
I'm gonna find a sea monster, too!
What crazy ideas are you hatching now, Luffy?
Uh... Ooh!
Hmm... Turtles?
Ah, too small.
Jeez.
We should try to rehabilitate him with something a little less sexy.
Hey, Nami, the direction we're taking isn't exactly the same way the log pose is pointing.
Oh, no problem. The correct course is technically southwest, so we're in the clear.
Yeah, but if we went in a straight line, we could get there a whole lot faster, couldn't we?
Well, if you go straight, you risk getting swept away in a sea current.
And if that should happen, you might run into an underwater mountain or a volcano, see? That's why.
Huh? Yikes! I'm with you on this one!
Yeah, but I thought all the currents here were dangerous. It is the Grand Line, after all.
So are you saying that some of them are actually stable?
Well, this one is.
That should do it. Now you stay put.
Hey! It's gonna start getting colder from here on out, so make sure you put on a coat or something!
You bring up a good point. I'm already starting to feel goosebumps on my skin.
Well, except for I...
You don't have any skin because you're a skeleton.
Chopper? Skull jokes are the only thing I have.
Please don't take that away from me.
We're going somewhere cold? Not the deep sea?
Don't you guys know the water's cold in the deep sea?
It's just like a bathtub. Hot water rises and cold sinks to the bottom.
Oh, does it? I don't take very many baths.
Aha! Because heat rises, and there's not much sunlight, so there's nothing to heat the water down here.
The temperature's not the only thing that's different at the bottom.
You're not still depressed, are you?
Once we move down, we'll find something called deep currents.
You don't run into them terribly often, but they're much larger than the regular currents.
Also, they're quite unique in that their flow is completely independent of what you see closer to the surface.
Currents? Under the currents? And you even have a diagram, huh?
You sure do know a lot of stuff.
That's because I'm so old.
Not only that, but all currents are connected to each other.
But that doesn't mean they have to flow in the same direction.
They flow east, west, up, and down.
It's like a big, long dragon, all tangled up.
The deep currents tend to travel at a surprisingly slow pace.
After they reach the deep sea, it takes approximately 2,000 years before they finally make their way up to the surface of the water.
That makes me feel young again, actually.
2,000?
Yes, 2,000.
And because of that, there are countless tales about what lurks within those deep, dark currents.
Monsters. Curses.
It's the wrath of the undead.
You mean the deep sea is haunted?
What? The sea's haunted?
Help!
That sounds fun to me!
Calm down, guys.
I don't know anything about the wrath of the undead, or whatever you're freaking out about,
but I do know that we'll encounter a downward flowing current soon.
Once we do, we should be able to ride it down into the deep sea.
Deep sea.
Surface.
Lows downward.
Flow.
She said something about deep sea currents. I don't know.
You morons can at least pretend like you understand me!
Shall we sing a duet, Nami?
Shut up!
I hear something.
It's here.
Nami, I see it.
Really?
Shut it up!
That's freaking sweet!
Whoa!
It's amazing.
I admit, whatever that thing is, it's pretty cool.
This one's called the downward plume.
Whoa!
It's almost like a giant waterfall!
Except underwater!
It's going so fast!
The sea is, like, falling into the sea, which doesn't make sense, but I like it!
Mother Nature, you're one crazy lady!
What a spectacular sight.
And from the looks of it, I'd say the stream runs fairly deep.
I've heard stories about these currents, but they did not do them justice.
It's crazy dark down there!
The floor so far, you can't even see it!
We're dead!
At this speed, we're going to get pile-driven straight down to the bottom!
You sure it's safe if we just go with the flow?
If you're worried about the ship, don't be!
Sunny was built from the treasure tree, Adam.
It's as tough as they come!
Okay!
Let's go!
Oh?
Is that...
Crap!
So it really does live down here!
It's no legend!
A demon that rules over the deep seas!
The enemy of all mankind!
Night!
Please listen to me, straw hats!
We have to turn back!
We're gonna die!
Oh yeah, I forgot you were here.
There's a sea monster!
Cut it out already!
There's no monster!
They're just stories!
Somebody made that up to scare people!
Lisa!
Jeez!
What is the matter with you guys?
Look!
Just spit it out!
Uh-oh!
Okay!
It's here!
Hey?
Waaaaa!
It's the Kraken!
No!
Oh, legendary giant octopus monster!
He made fish food out of those ships.
They left for the new world and never made it.
Turn around, please!
I'm not ready to die!
I beg you!
Just wait around for a couple days
and it'll probably go away!
Shut up for a sec!
I just had a perfect idea!
Guys!
We just have to capture it!
Huh?
Have you lost your mind, Loopy?
Well, if we catch it,
we can teach it how to pull the ship!
Like hell we can!
I tell you to take a quick look at it,
but it's so ridiculously huge,
I don't know how in the world
you can miss a damn thing!
Yuck, I didn't be!
I'm gonna die!
It must have been here for centuries!
The Kraken shows up in mist from all over the world!
It's one of the most terrible monsters that ever lived!
It doesn't have any bones.
And I am only bones.
That's interesting.
I wonder if it enjoys making no skull jokes.
Yeah, I doubt it!
What a hell of a scientist!
I don't know if it's a dead man.
I'm sorry.
You're a good artist!
I want to capture the moment on paper.
I wanted to capture the moment on paper.
Drawing pictures?!
Really?!
I'll help you out.
You've got a plan, right?
The problem is, there's not much we can do underwater.
No! No! No!
The problem is, the thing's gigantic!
We couldn't even take it on above sea level!
What is wrong with these people?
Anybody in their right mind would have run for the hills by now!
What's taking them so long to decide?
We're leaving! Shift the helm due south!
Hey, Nami! Let's go straight towards it!
Don't be stupid! That thing is-
It's okay, Nami. I'm here for-
Here for-
Who are you?
You held it in! Good job!
We made him all better!
Well, it helps that Nami put on a coat, too!
I'm not safe on this ship!
I'll have to protect myself!
Something's coming up behind us!
Huh?
Brother!
These guys again?
I'm so happy you came back for me!
Let's rush in there and rescue my bro!
You're the best crew a captain could ask for!
Stop it!
It destroyed the coating!
That ship's bigger than the sunny!
No!
They didn't make it!
Like jellyfish!
Damn it, RoRoNoah! That's too cruel!
Here it comes!
It's so huge!
There's no way we can fight against a monster like that!
No!
If you do that, you'll break the bubble for sure!
Chicken!
Voyage!
Can't we escape somehow?
Wait! Let me take care of it!
Don't go!
If you pop the bubble, then we all die!
The little fellow's right!
But if you want to face the crack in that badly,
I might just have the idea for you!
Fine! What is it? Make it snappy!
There! Perfect!
That contraption is called the Flutter Kick Coating!
It's an extravehicular diving suit!
As long as you stay inside it,
you can fight underwater as much as you need to!
Pretty amazing, right?
If I let them call the shots,
we'll all go to hell in a handbasket!
Hey! You weren't supposed to do that!
The rest of us wanted to get out of here!
Now they're going to stay and try to fight that thing!
I've been telling you all to run away from the beginning,
but your fearless leader was having none of us!
No!
But your fearless leader was having none of that,
now was he?
Think of it this way,
would you rather have to fight it outside
or fight it right here on the ship?
Right! You guys get out there!
Far, far away!
This rope's kinda annoying!
Remember to stay as far from this ship as you can!
Sure!
Well, you ready?
Yeah!
Huh? Wait a sec!
You guys forgot the safety ropes!
You're gonna get separated!
Sounds like Nami's worried about me!
Listen up!
I need both of you guys to distract him!
If I can get one good punch off,
I think I can take it!
Why don't I just slice into pieces?
It'd be easier!
Cause that wouldn't do me any good!
I wanna capture him and keep him as a pet!
Careful, guys!
Yeah, and keep your distance!
Cause every centimeter counts!
Okay, that was way too close!
Alright, stand back!
Frankie!
Rocket launcher!
Got him!
That was incredible!
Not another one!
How many arms does it have?
It's gonna hit us!
Huh?
Guard point!
Whoa, we hit the ship pretty hard!
Everyone okay?
He saved us!
Thanks, buddy!
Nice one, Chopper!
You're about to be crushed against that mountain!
Now, feel slow!
Higantezco mano!
Uh!
Whoa, those hands are big!
Look-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a!
Wow, those hands are big!
Nice one, Robin! That was close!
Thank goodness. I was only in the water for the briefest night, so my power held out.
Everybody did great! Now, guess it's my turn.
I'll use my new special move!
Third gear!
Luffy, Zoro, and Sanji leave the relative safety of the Sunny to face the Kraken in its own territory.
Putting their powerful new skills to work, they survive the encounter, only to be swept away by a downward current.
Now, separated from the rest of the crew, they become lost in the murky depths.
On the next One Piece, Lost in the Deep Sea, the Straw Hats get separated!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!
Let's action!
Press Noons Holiday
인이 Kai?
Seasel
Sir
Wow, that was a good drag?
Let's do that!
Go coach me!